

IGOR FILIN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



IGOR FILIN NAME:

PHONE: +7 960 594 2558

EMAIL: filinigor@yandex.ru











ABOUT ME

I am a frontend developer with Experience in creating SPAs using React, Redux, TypeScript. Knowledge of user interface, Testing and debugging. I improving my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with new technologies, such as Angular. I usually spend my free time reading IT-literature (David Flanagan, Philo Vladston Ferreira), Codewars and improving my English. Open to your suggestions.

SKILLS

- REACT/REDUX
- JAVASCRIPT/TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS/REST API
- UNIT TEST/JEST
- STORYBOOK
- MUI/ ANT DESIGN
- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- SNAPSHOT TEST
- GITHUB
- FORMIK
- FIGMA



WORK EXPERIENCE

MY PROJECT AS FRONTEND DEVELOPER (PART-TIME)

APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

• CARDS

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, Axios, React-Router-dom

SOCIAL NETWORK

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Axios, Ant-Design, React-Router-dom

• TODOLIST

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, MUI, Axios, React-Router-dom

• MOVIE DATABASE

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, MUI, Axios

CNC machine operator 2017 - 2022 (FULL-TIME) Writing programs and setting up CNC machines



EDUCATION

2022

IT-INCUBATOR Frontend developer

React/Redux/Typescript/JS

2019 - 2022

Tula State University

Engineer

2009 - 2012

Tula State Technological College



LANGUAGES

Russian: Native

English: A2 (in progress)